I'm Vlad Bibire, a student & front-end developer



Telephone 07425645866

Email vladbbr1@gmail.com

Portfolio vladb.uk

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/vladbbr/

Summary

Second-year Web Design & Development student, but a very keen front-end developer/graphic designer in my free time. I started 3 years ago by doing graphical website mockups, then I teached myself how to code in order to give my designs a real usage. At the moment, I try to perfect myself by creating component-based interfaces using the latest Javascript technologies, among with scalable CSS patterns and browser performance to offer the best user experience possible.

Skills Front-End Development

Passionate self-thought front-end developer using and learning constantly the latest web technologies. Detailed oriented person and fast learner, I can easily acquire new skills necessary for developing a certain type of project without loosing my focus on the deadline. Working in small teams made me become a very communicative person with good leadership skills that help when a problem occurs. I am a perfectionist and I love challanges, the harder the milestone, the more I enjoy it.

HTML - Jade

CSS - SCSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Materialize

Javascript - JS, ES6, NPM, React.js, Gulp.js, Webpack

Jekyll

Git & Github

Graphic Design

Profficient Photoshop user with a vast experience using it as a way to create different nouances and effects used on a web aplication, layered images for a parallax effect or image optimisation. Experienced in using Illustrator to develop SVG type imagery/icons and also vector style objects. Keen to create wireframes, prototypes and interfaces in Adobe XD.

Photoshop

Illustrator

XD

Experience

Web Developer & Designer

Solent Creatives · September 2017 - Present

Working as a partner freelancer. I mainly design and develop WordPress based websites for individuals and also I lead design projects, one of the most know client being Porche Portsmouth. The biggest project I was involved with was creating a website for Solent Aviation Art Society for which I ended up doing only the high fidelity user interface.

Freelance Graphic Designer in Romania

Self-Employed · May 2016 - April 2017

My first experience working with clients, doing most of the time branding on facebook, promoting events with ads made by myself and also small website designs.

Education

Bsc Web Design & Development

Solent University September 2017 - Present

Mathematics & Computer Science

"Alexandru Ioan Cuza" High School from Focsani, Romania September 2013 - July 2017

Graduated with 8.5 out of 10 general maximum points.